<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Export and Import Mod Settings</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.ExportAndImportModSettings</packageId>
  <author>Mlie</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/ExportAndImportModSettings</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/iCj5o7O.png[/img]

Ive gotten requests of adding exportable mod-settings to my mods from users that are putting together mod-packs and would like to bundle specific mod-settings with the pack.
Instead of implementing this per mod I wrote this mod instead.

This mod adds two small buttons at the top of the mod-options window for all mods (apart from HugsLib as that uses its own options-file for all mod-settings).
With these you can export the current mod-settings to a folder (default is the Desktop-folder but is changable in the mod-settings) and the file is then used to import the mod-settings.

The importing is done by overwriting the current settings with the imported file and then reloading the mod to apply the updated mod-settings. This can trigger warnings/errors depending on how the mod-settings are applied by the mod. If you notice some issues with a mods settings a simple way to reapply the imported settings is to restart the game.

There is also an option to export or import all active mods settings from this mods settings-window.

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://dsc.gg/mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/ExportAndImportModSettings][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/h5VwTNL.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Ds0rBAD.png[/img]
Since modding is just a hobby for me I expect no donations to keep modding. If you still want to show your support you can gift me anything from my [url=https://store.steampowered.com/wishlist/id/Mlie]Wishlist[/url] or buy me a cup of tea.

[url=https://ko-fi.com/G2G55DDYD][img]https://i.imgur.com/VWG0yff.png[/img][/url]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/5xwDG6H.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] or the standalone [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Uploader[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[*] Use [url=https://github.com/RimSort/RimSort/releases/latest]RimSort[/url] to sort your mods
[/list]

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/2937876372][img]https://img.shields.io/github/v/release/emipa606/ExportAndImportModSettings?label=latest%20version&amp;style=plastic&amp;labelColor=0070cd&amp;color=white[/img][/url]</description>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.5.0</modVersion>
</ModMetaData>